nutriliving.com 2013-10-22

# NutriLiving Privacy Policy | NutriLiving

NutriLiving Privacy Policy

April 23, 2013

The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways that NutriLiving.com (hereinafter, “NutriLiving”) treats the information You provide while using the [www.NutriLiving.com](http://www.nutriliving.com/) ("Website"). It is our goal to bring You information that is tailored to Your individual needs and, at the same time, protect Your privacy.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. You can access this Privacy Policy any time. Your use of and/or registration on any aspect of the Website will constitute Your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If You cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to the Website.

In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, please read our [User Agreement](http://www.nutriliving.com/content/nutriliving-user-agreement). Your use of the Website constitutes Your agreement to its terms and conditions of both this Privacy Policy and the User Agreement.

Each time You use the Website and/or any associated Applications, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply.  This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time.  For your reference, the date of the then current version will appear on this page. Continued access of the Website by You will constitute Your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the then current Privacy Policy.

 **INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES**

Traffic Data. NutriLiving automatically gathers information of the sort that browsers automatically make available, including: (i) IP addresses; (ii) domain servers; (iii) types of computers accessing the Website; and (iv) types of Web browsers accessing the Website (collectively “Traffic Data”). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify You.

Cookies. A “Cookie” is a string of information that a website stores on a user’s computer, and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the Website. The purpose of a Cookie is to identify the user as a unique user of the Website. NutriLiving uses Cookies to customize Your experience on the Website to Your interests, to ensure that You do not see the same advertisements or informational messages repeatedly, and to store Your password so You do not have to re-enter it each time You visit the Website. In addition, NutriLiving may use Cookies, and other methods, to store and retrieve data from Your web browser. 

IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO HAVE COOKIES PLACED ON YOUR COMPUTER, YOU SHOULD SET YOUR BROWSERS TO REFUSE COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN OF THE SERVICES AND CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF COOKIES. IF YOU REFUSE COOKIES, YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY.

Web Beacons. “Web Beacons” (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to Cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access Cookies. Unlike Cookies which are stored on the user’s computer hard drive, Web Beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages (or in e-mail). Web Beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with Cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. 

Personal Information. You will be asked to provide NutriLiving certain information related to You (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes, without limitation: (1) “Contact Data” (such as Your name and email address); and (2) “Demographic Data” (such as Your gender, birthday, zip code, country, height, weight, lifestyle and exercise frequency). The Personal Information You provide is used for such purposes as allowing You to set up a user account and profile, improving the content of the Website and/or Applications, customizing the advertising and content You see, and communicating with You about new features and other news. We may also draw upon this Personal Information in order to adapt the Website and/or Applications to Your needs, to research the effectiveness of our Website and/or Applications, and to develop new tools for our members.

You are under no obligation to provide Personal Information, with the caveat that Your refusal to do so may prevent You from using certain of the Services.

Information You Make Public. Certain portions of the Website and Applications are open to any viewer, such as our community forums and Your personal profile. Any information You post in these locations may be available and accessible to other members of the Website. In addition, the Website contains features that permit You to upload, post, transmit, display, perform or distribute content, information or other data, including Your Personal Information. Any information that You choose to disclose by means of such features becomes public information. You should exercise discretion when deciding to disclose Your Personal Information by means of such features, and You agree to assume all responsibility for doing so.

 **Uses**

We use this Personal Information to provide and improve our services, and to communicate with You.

NutriLiving will not sell or disclose Your Personal Information to third parties without Your explicit consent, except as specified in our Privacy Policy.

Special Notice to California Residents - **YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS** :

California Civil Code section 1798.83 (known as the "Shine the Light" law) requires NutriLiving.com to respond to requests from California customers inquiring about our business practices related to the disclosure of Personal Information to third parties and affiliated businesses for direct marketing purposes.  It is NutriLiving.com’s policy not to disclose member’s Personal Information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes, without first receiving Your express consent.  You may also exercise an option to “opt-out” of such information-sharing even after initially consenting to such information sharing.  If You wish to opt-out of our sharing of Your Personal Information with third parties or affiliates for direct marketing purposes or to find out more about Your opt-out rights or this Privacy Policy, please contact NutriLiving.com’s Privacy Coordinator at:  NutriLiving.com, PO Box 4574 Pacoima, California 91333 support@nutriliving.com].

In accordance with California law, You may opt-out of having Your Personal Information shared with third parties for their marketing purposes by contacting our Privacy Coordinator.  Additionally, if You wish to request updates or changes to Your information or Your preferences regarding receiving future promotional messages from NutriLiving.com, You may also contact our Privacy Coordinator or simply click on the website to be removed as a NutriLiving.com member.

 **Choices**

As a member You may review and change Your information in Your account settings, and You may remove certain optional pieces of information.

You may opt-out of receiving certain types of communications from NutriLiving in Your account settings.

You may disable cookies in Your web browser.

We endeavor to keep Your Personal Information secure. We maintain Your Personal Information on a secured, firewall protected server. We monitor the Website for evidence of fraudulent or improper behavior, reserving the right to remove inappropriate or illegal content.  Although Your web browser has privacy option settings that limit access to Your information, no security measures are perfect or failsafe.  We cannot control the actions of others with whom You share Your Personal Information and cannot guarantee that only authorized users will view Your Personal Information. You must utilize good judgment in protecting the privacy of Your Personal Information and employing good security practices like selecting a strong password and using updated antivirus software.  If You suspect any breach of security or Your Personal Information, please report the same immediately to our Privacy Coordinator. We must work together to assure the protection of Your Personal Information and the proper use of the Website.

 **Important Information**

If you have questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at support@nutriliving.com. 

We’ll communicate when we make changes to our Privacy Policy and we’ll update the revision date above.

 **Contact Us**

You can email us about the Privacy Policy at support@nutriliving.com.
